# MARINA SAMPROVALAKI

## MACHINE LEARNING ENGINEER

#### CONTACT

+306980884422

marina.samprovalaki@gmail.com

msamprovalaki.github.io

in linkedin.com/in/marina-samprovalaki/

github.com/msamprovalaki

tinyurl.com/3ymvdp5t

Athens, Greece

## EDUCATION

M.Sc. by Research, Computer Science

Athens University of Economics and Business

2023-2024

**B.Sc. in Informatics** 

Athens University of Economics and Business

2018-2022

-----

## LANGUAGES

English

#### PROFILE

I am currently pursuing an MSc in Computer Science, driven by a passion for exploring diverse areas of the field. My research focuses on advancing state-of-the-art Multimodal Large Language models in the medical domain, particularly in the area of medical image captioning.

# WORK EXPERIENCE

#### Researcher

Athens University of Economics and Business

10/2023 - today

 Researching Diagnostic Captioning with a focus on developing Multimodal Large Language Models to address the challenge of generating accurate and informative consults for medical images.

## **Junior Full Stack Engineer**

**HOMI Greece** 

11/2022 - 07/2023

- Data Modeling: Specialize in developing data models for predictive analytics and machine learning tasks.
- Cloud Platform Experience: Proficient in AWS for data storage and analysis..
- Frontend Frameworks: Experienced with React
- Dataase Technologies: Skilled with MongoDB and PostgreSQL.
- Web Application Development: Experienced in modern programming languages and frameworks, adept at making API calls.

# **Software Engineer Intern**

7L International

03/22 - 09/22

 Assisting in software development tasks, gaining hands-on experience in coding, debugging, and testing.